(Penny:)I will pay you back as soon as I can.
You just have to give me time.
- Oh, wait. You lent her money?
- She needed money.
(Penny:)You seem under pressure.
Did I not lend you a sufficient amount?
(Penny:)I can give you more.
(Penny:)Oh, you know, you would just love that,
wouldn't you?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)You would just love to open up
your little snake can...
(Penny:)...and throw some money at the girl
who can't pay her bills.
[SIGHS]
- Where are you going?
- Going home.
(Penny:)Where I won't be interrogated
like a criminal.
(Penny:)I forgot my fortune cookie.
(Sheldon:)In case either of you
have larceny in your heart...
(Sheldon:)...you should know that I've moved
my money out of the snake can.
(Leonard:)But if you're ever short, there's always
a couple of 50s in Green Lantern's ass.